

SKILLS

C++ HTML CSS

JavaScript

PHP

Node JS

MySQL Mongo DB

Bootstrap

Tailwind

Express

React

Next.Js

LET'S TALK

Phone:

+54 9 3826 441588

GitHub:

https://github.com/imrulii

Portfolio:

https://imrulii.github.io/david-portfolio/

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/davidariel-diaz/

Email:

Davidarield96@gmail.com

Diaz Jara David Ariel

Information Systems Analyst Jr. Full-Stack Developer

THIS IS MY HISTORY:

I was born in La Rioja - Argentina. I am 25 years old and I'm in the process of moving to Asuncion - Paraguay.

I'm a curious, analytic and proactive person who is always looking to grow personally and professionally.

I'm predisposed to learn new things, acquire more knowledge related to my field and to not rest until I dominate all the challenges that could arise, which I consider it's one of my strongest qualities, in addition to my commitment to work.

I like to work alone or with a team, adapting to new situations.

EDUCATION

Universidad Nacional de La Rioja (UNLAR - Campus Chamical)

INFORMATION SYSTEMS ANALYST

February 2016 - March 2023

The pre-project I presented for my tittle of Information Systems Analyst consisted in a web system with system security and interface to manage the data (CRUD) for a car dealership using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL and Bootstrap.

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION SYSTEMS

February 2016 - Present

Advanced student. Currently in 4th year.

EXPERIENCE

PETSHOP WEB SITE (FRONT-END)

April 2023 - May 2023

Full responsive Petshop web site developed with Next.Js and Tailwind

HOTEL WEB SITE (FRONT-END)

March 2023 - April 2023

Full responsive Hotel web site for a company using React and Tailwind

WEB SYSTEM E-COMMERCE (FULL-STACK)

February 2023 - Present

Developing a Web System for a store using MERN (Mongo DB, Express, React, Node JS)

CRUD WEB SYSTEM (FULL-STACK)

January 2023- March 2023

Pre-project that I made for my tittle of Information Systems Analyst

LANGUAGE

